Sheyla Cruz Castro

Software Developer

Professional profile

Graduate in Computer Science with advanced knowledge in programming and extensive experience in software development using leading technologies such as .Net and Angular. Additionally, I have skills in developing mobile applications with Flutter. I stand out for my proactive initiative and my ability to face challenges with creativity and resolution. With an approach focused on excellence and innovation, I constantly seek opportunities to significantly contribute to the success of projects and exceed expectations.

Work experience

• Freelance Frontend Developer, La Habana

January 2023 - February 2024:

Developed applications and modules with Angular, as well as APIs using Express.js as a Node.js framework and non-relational databases such as MongoDB.

- I implemented an authentication module for user registration and login using JWT.
- I designed an application for viewing and managing maps with MapBox.
- Developed a module to represent data through graphs using NgChartsModule.
- I created modules for searching and managing countries and images using APIs such as Rest Countries API and Giphy API respectively.

• Freelance Fullstack Developer, La Habana

October 2020 - December 2022:

- I led the creation of a system for the hospital sector company CPM Scientifica, aimed at managing and supervising the inventory of medical equipment, using ASP.Net MVC.
- At ChopiLand, I contributed to the development of an eCommerce for the sale of various items, using .NET Core.
- At mHealthApp, I was part of the team that developed a mobile application for the study of skin lesions, using Flutter, and software for image debugging, detection and subsequent classification of moles, using Python Flask.
- At SubzeroApi, I participated in the creation of software with authentication, reporting and modeling to control a delivery and storage system for frozen products, developed with .NET Core and PostgreSQL.
- I developed two cartographic mobile applications in their entirety: Surveyor Notifier. Surveyor to collect information associated with geolocatable properties and Nofiticator to notify that the survey of said properties was carried out, both developed with Flutter.

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science, University of Havana, Cuba September 2016 - December 2022

Personal information

36201 Vigo, Pontevedra (+34) 613 390 997 sheycruzcastro@gmail.com

Nationality

Cuban/Spanish

Links

Gitub LinkedIn Portafolio

Skills

- C#, .Net, ASPNet, .NetCore, WebForms
- Angular, JavaScript & TypeScript, Node.js, Express
- Flutter & Dart
- Python, Django, Flask
- HTML & CSS, SASS, LESS
- Bootstrap & PrimeNg & Material Design
- MySQL,PostgreSQL,
 SQLServer, MongoDB, Firebase
 Database
- Arq. de Microservicios & Arq. Orientada a Objetos
- SOLID & Buenas Prácticas
- AGILE, Unit Test & Integration Test
- Git & GitHub

Languages

Spanish - Native English - Intermediate

Hobbies

I am passionate about software development and staying up to date with the latest developments in science and technology. Additionally, I enjoy strategy games, sports and life in general.